gradesaver.com 2019-12-08

# Privacy Policy | GradeSaver

**Introduction:**

GradeSaver is dedicated to upholding the absolute privacy of all of our customers and clients. No information will ever be released concerning our customers except where GradeSaver is legally or ethically bound to do so. Please read through our Privacy Policy for additional information regarding use of your information.

This privacy policy covers what information we collect from you when you visit or register for our site, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. By using our site, you agree with the terms and conditions of this privacy policy and Terms of Use.

**Explanation of Type of Information Collected:**

When you use our site, we receive and collect certain information. Some information is automatically received and sometimes collected from you when you visit our site. We receive and collect the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet; the Internet protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using; the browser software you use and your operating system; the date and time you access our site; and the Internet address of the web site from which you linked directly to our site. We use this information to monitor the usage of our site.

**Description and Disclosure of How and For What Purpose Information is Collected:**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

Both GradeSaver and its third party advertisers (such as BurstMedia!, Advertising.com, and Google Adsense) use cookies to enhance your experience on our website. To find out more about how Burstmedia manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://www.burstmedia.com/>.

When you click on links and banners on our site that take you to third-party web sites, you will be subject to the third parties' privacy policies. While we support the protection of privacy on the Internet, GradeSaver cannot be responsible for the actions of any third-party web sites.

You can register with GradeSaver to view some of the information we have made available online, to post to message boards, or to order our products or services. Some features of our website require you to create a password-protected account with us. For setting up an account we require that you provide us with the following information: your name, email address and mailing address. When setting up the account, we ask you to create a password.

Additional information such as your credit card information may be requested if you are ordering a service. Credit card information is never stored by GradeSaver. We instead use a third party, currently Verisign, to protect all financial information.

**Your Access To and Ability To Change or Update Information:**

Your information may be changed by you at any time by going to the My Account section of our website. If you forget your password, you can go to /profile and request a new password. If you want to change your password or other account information, you can also do so at /forgot-password.

**Description of Safeguards and Security Measures Used to Protect Information:**

The account information you provide, including your credit card information, to establish an account with us and to make purchases from us is secured using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology. We use this SSL technology to prevent such information from being intercepted and read as it is transmitted over the Internet. The encrypted data goes to a secure site where your information is stored on restricted-access computers located at restricted-access sites.

To further secure your information, we require you to create a customer password when you establish an account with us. We encourage you to use a password that is not easily guessed. Keep your password secret; do not share it with anyone. The only way you can place an order with us online is by entering both your registered email address and password.

To further prevent unauthorized access to your account, remember that, after you log in, you should close out of your browser once you have finished accessing our website.

Under federal law, a credit card issuer cannot make you liable for charges in excess of $50.00 that result from the unauthorized use of your credit card. There are similar federal laws that relate to debit cards. Exceptions do apply, and you will have to comply with the rules of your credit card or debit card issuer, so please contact your card issuer for further details.

GradeSaver may release your information when we believe, in our good judgment, that such release is reasonably necessary to comply with law, enforce or apply the terms of any of our policies or user agreements, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of GradeSaver.com, our users, or others.

We reserve the right to modify or amend this policy at any time by posting the revised privacy policy on our site.
